[{"answer": "First thing I want to say is I'm loathe to be here frankly.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What do you want to say?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "On --", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "So, really, what's the real reason?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Here's what I see just a fundamental flaw in the American gun culture.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "What are we afraid of?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, this is the continuing problem I have with all my movies.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Did you expect the impact of both the massacre in Columbine and your movie to have more effect than it's had?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "And do you see any link between that and these sorts of incidents?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Makes it easier, though, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "How do you deal with the constitutional divide that America has over how that is interpreted?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I guess they're afraid to.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "It's -- no, I think it -- actually, it's -- it's more because we're easy -- we're easily scared than other people in other countries.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "That is why America is seeing such an escalation in its gun ownership, isn't it?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I think it -- it's a fascinating question and I think it's one that many Americans are wrestling with.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "What is it about us that we are so cruel to each other?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Well, this is the point, isn't it.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "We're -- we're -- you know, where are you going to draw the line here with this?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "On this point, a clear example, to me, of the kind of thing you're talking about is the Trayvon Martin case, where George Zimmerman, if he hadn't been carrying a gun, indisputably Trayvon Martin would still be alive.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Who do you think is going to come into your house?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "There is an irony that it's George Zimmerman using Florida's \"stand your ground\" defense when, in fact, as you say, you could equally argue that Trayvon Martin may well have been doing the same thing.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Doesn't Trayvon Martin actually have the right to kill George Zimmerman if George Zimmerman is stalking him and -- and the police have told him not to stalk him?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Is it time that America just woke up and dealt properly with mental health generally?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Not too good.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "When you knew that picture was coming out, how did you feel?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "HELPS: Like the worst in the world, you know, like the lowest of the low.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What is that feeling like?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "You know, I think my mom has always been obviously how all moms are.", "docId": "120729pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "How did you brace yourself for that?", "qSentId": 612}]